Finding Aid for the Julian Goodman Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Articles/Congressional Testimonies/Speeches by JG
  - Speeches
    - B’nai B’rith Award to J. Harris, Annual Banquet, Houston, Texas, September 28, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 10.)
    - B’nai B’rith Award to J. Harris, Annual Banquet, Houston, Texas, September 28, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 11.)
    - B’nai B’rith Award to J. Harris, Annual Banquet, Houston, Texas, September 28, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 12.)
    - WTRF TV 25th Anniversary, Wheeling, West Virginia, October 27, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 13.)
  - Speeches
    - WTRF TV 25th Anniversary, Wheeling, West Virginia, October 27, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 1.)
    - WTRF TV 25th Anniversary, Wheeling, West Virginia, October 27, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 2.)
    - WTRF TV 25th Anniversary, Wheeling, West Virginia, October 27, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 3.)
    - South Carolina Broadcasters Association, November 21, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 4.)
    - Dinner Honoring Dero Downing, Bowling Green, Kentucky, December 14, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 5.)
    - Dinner Honoring Dero Downing, Bowling Green, Kentucky, December 14, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 6.)
    - Speech Material - Gannetteer, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 7.)
    - Speech Material, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 8.)
    - National Association of Broadcasters Annual Meeting, March 25, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 9.)
    - General Federation of Women’s Club, New Orleans, Louisiana, June 5, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 10.)
    - “The First Amendment as an Absolute” The Washington Journalism Center, Washington D.C. –Frank E. Gannett Lecture, June 7, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 11.)
    - “The First Amendment as an Absolute” The Washington Journalism Center, Washington D.C. – Frank E. Gannett Lecture, June 7, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 12.)
    - “The First Amendment as an Absolute” The Washington Journalism Center, Washington D.C. – Frank E. Gannett Lecture, June 7, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 13.)
    - “The First Amendment as an Absolute” The Washington Journalism Center, Washington D.C. – Frank E. Gannett Lecture, June 7, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 14.)
    - “The First Amendment as an Absolute” The Washington Journalism Center, Washington D.C. – Frank E. Gannett Lecture, June 7, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 15.)
    - Introduction to Julian Goodman – Washington Area Broadcasters Association, June 14, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 16.)
  - Speeches
    - Introduction to Julian Goodman – Washington Area Broadcasters Association, June 14, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 1.)
    - Ted Yates and Stuart Schulberg, July 2, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 2.)
    - Kentucky Broadcasters Association, Louisville, Kentucky, August 25, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 3.)
    - “The First Amendment in the 80’s” Journalism Alumni Seminar, February 16, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 4.)
    - Chamber of Commerce, Paducah, Kentucky, March 6, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 5.)
    - “The ‘Roast’ of Walter Cronkite” Washington Correspondents, March 20, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 6.)
    - Speech Material, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 7.)
    - Deadline Club, New York City Chapter, March 16, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 8.)
    - Russ Tornabene, Ernie Pyle Memorial Lecture, March 16, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 9.)
    - University of Kentucky Hall of Fame, April 13, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 10.)
    - “Ethics and the Media” Larchmont Avenue Presbyterian Church, September 27, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 11.)
    - Associated Press Material, October 1, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 12.)
    - National Association of Broadcasters – First Amendment Panel, Dallas, Texas, April 7, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 13.)
    - Introduction to John Chancellor at the University of Nevada Reno Foundation Dinner, November 19, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 14.)
    - Senior Men’s Association Larchmont Avenue Church (w/ audio cassette), October 17, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 15.)
    - Senior Men’s Association Larchmont Avenue Church, October 17, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 16.)
    - “Your Business is Different” keynote address at University of Georgia School of Journalism- Di Gamma Kappa Distinguished Achievement Award, January 21, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 17.)
    - Draft for K. Graham, May 1987 (Box 25, Folder 18.)
    - Draft #2 Olympics 1988, August 9, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 19.)
  - Speeches
    - Speech Material, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 1.)
    - IRTS (International Radio and Television Society), March 2, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 2.)
    - 84th Dinner of the Kentuckians of New York, May 1989 (Box 26, Folder 3.)
    - Incomplete Text, Remarks by Julian Goodman, Undated (Box 26, Folder 4.)
    - Speech Material on First Amendment (1), Undated (Box 26, Folder 5.)
    - Speech Material on First Amendment (2), Undated (Box 26, Folder 6.)
    - Remarks on Roone Arledge and TV News, Undated (Box 26, Folder 7.)
    - Speech Material, Miscellaneous (1), Undated (Box 26, Folder 8.)
    - Speech Material, Miscellaneous (2), Undated (Box 26, Folder 9.)
    - Speeches and Testimony – Indexes (Box 26, Folder 10.)
    - Index to Julian Goodman Speeches, Articles, Testimony – 25 pages – Pre 1963-1978 (Box 26, Folder 11.)
    - Index to Speeches and Articles – 1966-1978 with reprint titles (Box 26, Folder 12.)
  - Speeches by others
    - Abrams, Floyd – “Are Some Corporation ‘More Equal’ Than Others?” National Legal Center for the Public Interest, March 15, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 13.)
    - Daley, Mayor Richard J. – Speech to National Restaurant Association, May 21, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 14.)
    - Ferris, Charles D. (Chairman FCC) – Address IRTS, September 20, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 15.)
    - Frank, Reuven – Keynote Address at RTNDA, Hollywood, Florida, December 3, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 16.)
    - Goldwater, Senator Barry –Republican Presidential Nomination Acceptance Speech, July 16, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 17.)
    - Kennan, George F. – “America After Vietnam” Williamsburg, Virginia, June 1, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 18.)
    - Meaney, Don – Georgia Radio TV Institute, January 22, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 19.)
    - Pfeiffer, Jane C. – Address at NBC Affiliate Convention, May 15, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 20.)
    - Silverman, Fred, NBC President – NBC Progress Report, April 1979 (Box 26, Folder 21.)
    - Silverman, Fred, NBC President – Remarks at NBC – TV Affiliate Convention, Los Angeles, California, May 15, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 22.)
    - Weinblatt, Mike – Address at NBC Affiliate Convention, May 15, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 23.)
    - Unknown – Typescript – 20 Pages (Box 26, Folder 24.)
- NBC Corporate – Affiliates
  - Affiliates
    - Archinard, Paul – France, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1.)
    - VIS News, 1964-1966 (Box 27, Folder 2.)
    - Board of Delegates – Minutes of Meetings, New York City, 1966; March 2 (Box 27, Folder 3.)
    - Board of Delegates – Minutes of Meetings, Nassau – November 15-16, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 4.)
    - Board of Delegates, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 5.)
    - Meetings, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 6.)
    - Meetings, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 7.)
    - Board of Delegates, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 8.)
    - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 9.)
    - Board of Delegates, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 10.)
    - CATV, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 11.)
    - Convention, New York, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 12.)
    - Correspondence, January-March, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 13.)
    - Correspondence, April – June, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 14.)
    - Correspondence, July-September, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 15.)
    - Correspondence, October-November, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 15.)
  - Affiliates
    - Board of Delegates, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 1.)
    - Correspondence, January-February, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 2.)
    - Correspondence, February-March, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 3.)
    - Correspondence, March-May, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 4.)
    - Correspondence, May, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 5.)
    - Correspondence, May-June, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 6.)
    - Correspondence, July-August, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 7.)
    - Correspondence, August-September, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 8.)
    - Correspondence, October, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 9.)
    - Correspondence, October-November, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 10.)
    - Correspondence, November, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 11.)
    - Correspondence, November, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 12.)
  - Affiliates
    - Correspondence, December, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 1.)
    - Correspondence, December, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 2.)
    - Meetings, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 3.)
    - Meetings, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 4.)
    - Meetings, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 5.)
    - Board of Delegates, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 6.)
    - VIS News, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 7.)
    - Board of Delegates, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 8.)
    - Convention, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 9.)
    - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 10.)
    - Board of Delegates, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 11.)
    - VIS News, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 12.)
    - 1974 (Box 29, Folder 13.)
    - 1975 (Box 29, Folder 14.)
    - NIS National News and Information Service, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 15.)
    - National News Information Service – NIS/Radio, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 16.)
  - Affiliates
    - Board of Delegates, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 1.)
    - Board of Delegates, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 2.)
    - Board of Delegates, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 3.)
    - Convention – 50th Anniversary, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 4.)
    - Convention – 50th Anniversary, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 5.)
    - Convention – 50th Anniversary, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 6.)
    - Correspondence, January, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 7.)
    - Correspondence, February, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 8.)
    - Correspondence, March-April, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 9.)
    - Correspondence, May, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 10.)
    - Correspondence, June, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 11.)
    - Correspondence, July, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 12.)
  - Affiliates
    - Correspondence, July, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 1.)
    - Correspondence, August, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 2.)
    - Correspondence, September-October, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 3.)
    - Correspondence, November-December, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 4.)
    - General Foods– Correspondence, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 5.)
    - Radio Division Financial Report, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 6.)
    - Station Relations, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 7.)
    - Remarks by Fred Silverman and Ed Griffiths, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 8.)
    - WIS-TV Silver Anniversary – Correspondence with Senator Strom Thurmond, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 9.)
    - United Press International – Memorandum, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 10.)
    - Convention, Los Angeles, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 11.)
    - Meeting Summary (1), 1983 (Box 31, Folder 12.)
    - Meeting Summary (2) Charts, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 13.)
    - Meetings Summary, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 14.)
    - Convention, Los Angeles, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 15.)
- NBC Corporate – People
  - People
    - Abernethy, Robert G. and Jean Montgomery 2. Adams, David C.- personal correspondence (Box 32, Folder 1.)
    - Adams, David C., 1967 (Box 32, Folder 3.)
    - Adams, David C., 1968 – February – July (Box 32, Folder 4.)
    - Adams, David C., 1968 – August 19 -22 (Box 32, Folder 5.)
    - Adams, David C., 1968 – August 23 (Box 32, Folder 6.)
    - Adams, David C., 1968 – August 30-December (Box 32, Folder 7.)
    - Adams, David C., 1969 – January-November (Box 32, Folder 8.)
    - Adams, David C., 1971 (Box 32, Folder 9.)
    - Adams, David C., 1975-1979 (Box 32, Folder 10.)
    - Announcements, February 1974 (Box 32, Folder 11.)
    - Bartelme, Joe, 1977 – Re: Jane Crawford Lenihan (Box 32, Folder 12.)
    - Beville, Hugh (Mal), 1967-1970 (Box 32, Folder 13.)
    - Blair, Frank, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 14.)
    - Bourgholtzer, Frank (Box 32, Folder 15.)
    - Brinkley, David, 1950-1962 (Box 32, Folder 16.)
    - Brinkley, David, 1963-1965 (Box 32, Folder 17.)
    - Brinkley, David, 1966-1968 (Box 32, Folder 18.)
    - Brinkley, David, 1970-1972 (Box 32, Folder 19.)
    - Brinkley, David, 1974-1976 (Box 32, Folder 20.)
    - Brinkley, David, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 21.)
    - Brinkley, David, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 22.)
    - Brinkley, David, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 23.)
  - People
    - Brinkley, David, 1981- August 3rd-September 5 (Box 33, Folder 1.)
    - Brinkley, David, 1981 – September 6- September 9 (Box 33, Folder 2.)
    - Brinkley, David, 1981 – September 11 (Box 33, Folder 3.)
    - Brinkley, David, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 4.)
    - Brinkley, David, 1987-1988 (Box 33, Folder 5.)
    - Brinkley, David, 1991-1996, undated (Box 33, Folder 6.)
    - Brokaw, Tom (Box 33, Folder 7.)
    - Burns, George (Box 33, Folder 8.)
    - Burr, Raymond (Ironsides) (Box 33, Folder 9.)
    - Carroll, Diahann (Box 33, Folder 10.)
    - Carson, Johnny (Box 33, Folder 11.)
    - Chancellor, John, 1962-1974 (Box 33, Folder 12.)
    - Chancellor, John, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 13.)
    - Chancellor, John, 1978-1983 (Box 33, Folder 14.)
    - Clay, George, death 1964 (Box 33, Folder 15.)
    - Coggins, Joseph Brendan (Box 33, Folder 16.)
    - Coleman, Gary (Diff’rent Strokes) (Box 33, Folder 17.)
    - Conrad, Anthony L., 1975 (Box 33, Folder 18.)
    - Conrad, Anthony L., 1976 – January-March (Box 33, Folder 19.)
    - Conrad, Anthony L., 1976 – April-May (Box 33, Folder 20.)
    - Conrad, Anthony L., 1976 – June (Box 33, Folder 21.)
    - Conrad, Anthony L., 1976 – July (Box 33, Folder 22.)
    - Conrad, Anthony L., 1976 – September-October (Box 33, Folder 23.)
    - Conrad, Anthony L., 1976-1984 – Newspaper Clippings (Box 33, Folder 24.)
    - Considine, Robert – Radio Programs (Box 33, Folder 25.)
    - Cosby, Bill (Box 33, Folder 26.)
    - Crystal, Les (Box 33, Folder 27.)
    - Derby, Joseph (Box 33, Folder 28.)
    - Directors Lists (Box 33, Folder 29.)
    - DuBrow, Rick (Box 33, Folder 30.)
    - Dunkel, Don, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 31.)
  - People
    - Durgin, Don (Box 34, Folder 1.)
    - Ebersol, Dick (Box 34, Folder 2.)
    - Eid, Leif (Box 34, Folder 3.)
    - Eiges, Sydney H. (Box 34, Folder 4.)
    - Ervin, Thomas E., 1969-1976 (Box 34, Folder 5.)
    - Executives Birthdays – List dated 11/75 (Box 34, Folder 6.)
    - Executive Personnel, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 7.)
    - Executive Personnel, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 8.)
    - Executives – Fuchs, George; Lindeman, Carl; Corcoran, Charles; Weinblatt, Myron; Tebet, David (Box 34, Folder 9.)
    - Frank, Reuven, 1965-1967 (Box 34, Folder 10.)
    - Frank, Reuven, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 11.)
    - Frank, Reuven – Statement Re: Democratic National Convention 1968 and Reporters’ Summary (Box 34, Folder 12.)
    - Frank, Reuven – “The Ugly Mirror” Address, September 30, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 13.)
    - Frank, Reuven, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 14.)
    - Frank, Reuven, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 15.)
    - Frank, Reuven – “A Hindsight Saga” Address, February 17, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 16.)
    - Frank, Reuven – Address, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 17.)
    - Frank, Reuven, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 18.)
    - Frank, Reuven – “If Benjamin Franklin Had Invented Television” Address, June 22, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 19.)
    - Frank, Reuven, 1972-1977 (Box 34, Folder 20.)
    - Frank, Reuven – Profile in Washington Journalism Review vol.4, no. 6, July/August 1982 (Box 34, Folder 21.)
    - Frank, Reuven, 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 22.)
    - Frank, Reuven, 1984-1989 (Box 34, Folder 23.)
    - Freed, Fred – NBC Specials (Box 34, Folder 24.)
    - Friedman, Paul (Box 34, Folder 25.)
  - People
    - Fuchs, George, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1.)
    - Fuchs, George, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 2.)
    - Garagiola, Joe (Box 35, Folder 3.)
    - Gardam, David (Box 35, Folder 4.)
    - Garroway, Dave (Box 35, Folder 5.)
    - Gerber, Jay (Box 35, Folder 6.)
    - Gerber, John W., 1956 (Box 35, Folder 7.)
    - Godwin, Earl (Box 35, Folder 8.)
    - Grams, Harold (Box 35, Folder 9.)
    - Green, Gerald (Box 35, Folder 10.)
    - Hagan, Chet (Box 35, Folder 11.)
    - Hangen, Welles, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 12.)
    - Hangen, Welles, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 13.)
    - Hangen, Welles, 1972-1974 (Box 35, Folder 14.)
    - Hangen, Welles, 1975- 1984 (Box 35, Folder 15.)
    - Hangen, Welles – Legal documents, 1978-1981 (Box 35, Folder 16.)
    - Hangen, Welles – Tell Him That I Heard – Typescript by Pat Hangen, 1975 coverpagep. 31 (Box 35, Folder 17.)
    - Hangen, Welles -- Tell Him That I Heard – Typescript by Pat Hangen, 1975 p. 32 - 95 (Box 35, Folder 18.)
    - Hangen, Welles -- Tell Him That I Heard – Typescript by Pat Hangen, 1975 p. 96-150 (Box 35, Folder 19.)
    - Hangen, Welles -- Tell Him That I Heard – Typescript by Pat Hangen, 1975 p. 151-Epilogue (Box 35, Folder 20.)
    - Harkness, Richard (Box 35, Folder 21.)
    - Hartz, Jim (Box 35, Folder 22.)
    - Hazam, Lou, 1961-1963 (Box 35, Folder 23.)
    - Hazam, Lou, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 24.)
  - People
    - Hazam, Lou, 1963-1986 (Box 36, Folder 1.)
    - Hazam, Lou, death - 1983 (Box 36, Folder 2.)
    - Heinemann, George – “Looking at Children’s Television” – article, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 3.)
    - Heinemann, George, 1973-1975 (Box 36, Folder 4.)
    - Heinemann, George, 1976-1981 (Box 36, Folder 5.)
    - Heitzner, Irving, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 6.)
    - Henry, Bill (Box 36, Folder 7.)
    - Hope, Bob (Box 36, Folder 8.)
    - Hubbard, Stanley (Box 36, Folder 9.)
    - Huntley, Chet, 1960-1965 (Box 36, Folder 10.)
    - Huntley, Chet, 1967-1970 (Box 36, Folder 11.)
    - Huntley, Chet, 1970-1991 (Box 36, Folder 12.)
    - Huntley, Tippy (Mrs.William Conrad) (Box 36, Folder 13.)
    - Jarvis, Lucy, 1969-1976 (Box 36, Folder 14.)
    - Jones, Charles O., 1985 (Box 36, Folder 15.)
    - Kasmire, Robert – 1969 – 1974; Cartoon, original (Box 36, Folder 16.)
    - Kasmire, Robert – 1975 – Hampshire College (Box 36, Folder 17.)
    - Kearns, Tom (Box 36, Folder 18.)
    - Kennedy, William (Box 36, Folder 19.)
    - Kenney, Peter, 1971-1976 (Box 36, Folder 20.)
    - Kiermaier, John – William Paley Foundation – Museum of Broadcasting (Box 36, Folder 21.)
  - People
    - Kintner, Robert E., August 11, 1960-May 24, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 1.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., May 25,1961-October 30, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 2.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., November 3, 1961-December 21, 1961; undated (Box 37, Folder 3.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., 1961 – Trip Around the World (Box 37, Folder 4.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., January 1962 (Box 37, Folder 5.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., February 1962 (Box 37, Folder 6.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., March 1962 (Box 37, Folder 7.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., April 1962 (Box 37, Folder 8.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., May 1962 (Box 37, Folder 9.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., June - July 25, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 10.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., July 27, 1962 - August 17, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 11.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., August 17 - October 29, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 12.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., November 1 - December 18, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 13.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., 1963 (Box 37, Folder 14.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., July 1964 (Box 37, Folder 15.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., August 1964 (Democratic National Convention) – December 1964 (Box 37, Folder 16.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., January 1965 (Box 37, Folder 17.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., February - August 1965 (Box 37, Folder 18.)
  - People
    - Kintner, Robert E. – September, December 1965 (Box 38, Folder 1.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., 1965 (Box 38, Folder 2.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., April 1965; “Broadcasting and the News” in Harper’s (Box 38, Folder 3.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., 1966 (Box 38, Folder 4.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., 1967 (Box 38, Folder 5.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., 1968 (Box 38, Folder 6.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., 1969 (Box 38, Folder 7.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., 1970 (Box 38, Folder 8.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., 1971 (Box 38, Folder 9.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., 1972 (Box 38, Folder 10.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., 1974 (Box 38, Folder 11.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., 1975 - 1977 (Box 38, Folder 12.)
    - Kintner, Robert E., 1979 (Box 38, Folder 13.)
    - Kintner, Robert E. –Death and Obituaries, December 19, 1980; 1981; Tribute by Julian Goodman (Box 38, Folder 14.)
    - Kissinger, Henry (consultant to NBC News) (Box 38, Folder 15.)
    - Klein, Paul (Box 38, Folder 16.)
    - Kuralt, Charles, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 17.)
    - Lamb, John, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 18.)
    - Lamb, John, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 19.)
    - Laginestra, Rocco M. (Box 38, Folder 20.)
    - Lawrence, William (New York Times, ABC News Reporter) – memorial service remarks (Box 38, Folder 21.)
    - Lemon, Robert, 1972-74 (Box 38, Folder 22.)
    - Lemon, Robert – Death, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 23.)
    - Lindemann, Carl (Box 38, Folder 24.)
    - Lower, Elmer, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 25.)
    - MacNeil, Robert, 1964-1965 (Box 38, Folder 26.)
  - People
    - Manning, Gordon (Box 39, Folder 1.)
    - McAndrew, William, 1963-1968 (Box 39, Folder 2.)
    - McAndrew, William C. (President, NBC news), 1968 (obituaries) (Box 39, Folder 3.)
    - McAndrew, William C. (President, NBC news), 1968; (letters at the time of his death) (Box 39, Folder 4.)
    - McAndrew, William C. (President, NBC news), 1968 (letters at the time of his death) (Box 39, Folder 5.)
    - McCormick, Robert (Box 39, Folder 6.)
    - McGannon, Donald H. – President and Chairman Westinghouse Broadcasting Co, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 7.)
    - McGannon, Donald H. – President and Chairman Westinghouse Broadcasting Co, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 8.)
    - McGee, Frank, 1963; 1974 (Box 39, Folder 9.)
    - Monderer, Howard (Box 39, Folder 10.)
    - Monroe, Bill (Box 39, Folder 11.)
    - Mulholland, Robert E. (Box 39, Folder 12.)
    - Nelson, Tom (Box 39, Folder 13.)
    - Nessen, Ron, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 14.)
    - Nessen, Ron, 1975; The White House (Box 39, Folder 15.)
    - Newman, Edwin (Box 39, Folder 16.)
    - News Correspondents (Box 39, Folder 17.)
    - News Domestic Bureaus, 1976-1988 (Box 39, Folder 18.)
    - News – Foreign Bureaus (Box 39, Folder 19.)
    - Northshield, Shad (Box 39, Folder 20.)
    - Pauley, Jane (Box 39, Folder 21.)
    - Paxton, Fred (head of NBC affiliates), 1980 (Box 39, Folder 22.)
    - Pfeiffer, Jane, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 23.)
    - Pfeiffer, Jane, 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 24.)
    - Rich, John (Box 39, Folder 25.)
    - Rieger, Hank (Box 39, Folder 26.)
    - Rosen, George (Box 39, Folder 27.)
    - Rowe, Gerald (Box 39, Folder 28.)
  - People
    - Royal, John F., 1969-1976 (Box 40, Folder 1.)
    - Royal, John F., Obituary; 1978 (Box 40, Folder 2.)
    - Rubin, Aaron (executive V.P.), 1972 (Box 40, Folder 3.)
    - Rubin, Aaron (executive V.P.) – Obituary, December 1987 (Box 40, Folder 4.)
    - Rukeyser, Meryle S. Jr., 1975 (Box 40, Folder 5.)
    - Salant, Richard S. (Box 40, Folder 6.)
    - Sarnoff, David (Box 40, Folder 7.)
    - Sarnoff, Robert W. (Box 40, Folder 8.)
    - Sarnoff, Robert, 1971-1974 (Box 40, Folder 9.)
    - Savitch, Jessica (Box 40, Folder 10.)
    - Scherer, Ray, 1954-1972 (Box 40, Folder 11.)
    - Scherer, Ray, 1973-1984 (Box 40, Folder 12.)
    - Schlosser, Herbert S. (Box 40, Folder 13.)
    - Schlosser, Herb, 1975-1980 (Box 40, Folder 14.)
    - Schnazer, Ken (Box 40, Folder 15.)
    - Schulberg, Stuart – memorial, July 2, 1979; 1976 (Box 40, Folder 16.)
    - Scott, Walter D. – “Broadcasting and the New Audience” – 1966; “The Color of Television Revolution”, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 17.)
    - Scott, Walter D., 1966-1970 (Box 40, Folder 18.)
    - Scott, Walter D., 1971-1973 (Box 40, Folder 19.)
    - Scott, Walter D., 1974 (Box 40, Folder 20.)
    - Scott, Walter D., 1975 (Box 40, Folder 21.)
  - People
    - Scott, Walter D., 1976 - 1977 (Box 41, Folder 1.)
    - Scott, Walter D., 1978 (Box 41, Folder 2.)
    - Scott, Walter D., 1979-1992 (Box 41, Folder 3.)
    - Scott, Willard (Today Show) (Box 41, Folder 4.)
    - Shalit, Gene (Box 41, Folder 5.)
    - Sharkey, Sam (Box 41, Folder 6.)
    - Shore, Dinah (Box 41, Folder 7.)
    - Silverman, Fred, 1978 --Jan-Jun (Box 41, Folder 8.)
    - Silverman, Fred, 1978 – Jun-Dec (Box 41, Folder 9.)
    - Silverman, Fred, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 10.)
    - Silverman, Fred, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 11.)
    - Silverman, Fred, 1980-86 (Box 41, Folder 12.)
    - Skelton, Red (Box 41, Folder 13.)
    - Small, Bill (Box 41, Folder 14.)